Bikini Jones and the Temple of Eros is a comedy film directed by Fred Olen Ray.
Bikini Jones is on the hunt for the lost Temple of Eros.
Using a golden idol as her guide, she searches the wild land of Moronica, along the way
battling man-eating dinosaurs and fending off the sensuously wicked Evilla.
Bikini will do anything to find the sacred temple...
and certainly does (much to the delight of her fans)!
Bikini Jones, played by Christine Nguyen.
Evilla Cruella, played by Heather Vandeven.
Carol Summers, played by Rebecca Love.
Drago, played by Frankie Cullen.
Mark X, played by Billy Chappell.
Security Guard, played by Brynn Tyler.
Bikini Jones and the Temple of Eros is a 2010 American made-for-cable comedy erotic film written
and directed by Fred Olen Ray (under the pseudonym name Nicholas Juan Medina).
It is a porn spoof of Indiana Jones.
The tone is lighthearted.